SANA RZGAR

CONTACT INFORMATION

EMAIL: sanarizgar34@gmail.com

LOCATION: Sulaymaniyah

PHONE: (964)750 116 9342

GITHUB: <u>https://github.com/Sanaa00</u>

SKILLS

HTML

- CSS
- Java Script
- SQL
- MongoDb
- TailwindCss
- Git/Github
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- TypeScript
- Npm
- Next is
- Node js (Express js)

CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

- Freelance mentorship program
- Programming with java script (coursera)
- React (coursera)

OBJECTIVE

I'm Sana, Software Engineer & Front-end developer, I have been in Graphic design field for several years, I try to use my technical skills with dedication & sincerity for the benefit of company and to achieve new heights in my career.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVLOPER

| 2022 - Present

I selected web development as my professional career & create some small projects & do all my best to growing fast as I can

LECTURER

Chra private institute. Chamchamal | 2021 - 2022

LECTURER ASSISTANT

Charmo University. Chamchamal | 2021 - 2022

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

White Icon. Sulaymaniyah | 2022

EDUCATION

BACHELOR

Salahaddin University Erbil | 2018 - 2021

BOOTCAMP

WeCode Erbil | 2022

BOOTCAMP

Bit Sulaymaniyah | 2023